https://www.magickalneeds.com/privacy-policy/

$0.00 0 items
No products in the cart.
$0.00 0 items
No products in the cart.
Updated April 30th, 2018
This privacy policy sets out how Magickal Needs uses and protects any information that you give Magickal Needs when you use this website. Magickal Needs is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Magickal Needs may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information: name, contact information including email address, demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests, shipping information for purchases delivery, and other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided if you opted into our Newsletter mailing.  You may opt out any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may occasionally contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Google Analyics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).  Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage.  Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.  You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.  By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at skye@magickalneeds.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998 and the GDPR of 2018 Act.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Commitment to Data Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Services and Web sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers” from illegally obtaining this information. We take all reasonable measures to prevent such breaches of security, but given the resourcefulness of cyber-criminals we are unable to guarantee that our security is 100% breach-proof. You assume the risk of such breaches to the extent that they occur despite our reasonable security measures.  In the event of a breach, you will be notified immediately.
term papermla dissertation term paper help
write papers online
Butterfly weed attracts hummingbirds together with butterflies.
Individuals are certain to have a fast and straightforward method of purchasing https://www.potlala.com weed.
Fortunately, creating your own weed and feed is simple to accomplish, and the outcomes are gentle and successful on lawns.
Spray over the weeds you need to kill.
Spray liberally through the region of your lawn where you would like to control the weeds.
To spend less, you can earn a weed and feed at home.
So, it’s imperative you know your wellbeing status now. Naturally, you’ll have to speak to your health care provider initially and set up an appointment time.
Thus, even when you get a medical marijuana card, but you need to fly a 757, you’ve got to make certain your healthcare marijuana’s effect has passed, when you board your pilot seat.
Provided you can show that you require marijuana to take cannabis card care of a health condition, it’s within your right to utilize it freely.
“
Not all animals are equipped to supply the sort of support required to assist you with your mental health symptoms.
An emotional support animal is an excellent means to aid with many problems.
Emotional support animals aren’t a scam.
If you’re in the usa, you might have heard of emotional support animal or ESA.
